<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SBAuction</string>
    <string name="agreement">Agree to Terms Before Using:\nThis app has been provided to you free of charge. You do not have to pay for any part of this app, the purchases are donations,
    and you do not receive anything extra for giving money besides the satisfaction you get from supporting something that benefits you.
    Furthermore, there will be no ads in this app, if you wanted more reason to support what I do here.
    This app is designed to attempt to give you extra information that may benefit you while you play Skyblock.
        However, the information provided within does not constitute legal trading advice, if you utilize any of the
        information given to you by this app and lose any virtual currency, the author is not responsible for your loss.
    This software was not designed with malicious intent, but the author will not be responsible for any damages to your
     physical device that result from the usage of this app. By clicking agree below, you acknowledge that you use
    this app at your own risk, and you will not hold the author responsible for any damages. If you do not agree
    to these terms, uninstall this app.</string>
    <string name="nerd_info">Well, you probably want something to do while you wait for stuff to load.
    So, for the people that actually know how things work, I figured I might as well explain what\'s going on in this page.
    Hypixel stores 1000 auctions per page, located at differing URLS. As you probably saw, it didn\'t take super long to contact
    Hypixel API and retrieve the first page, along with information on how many more pages there are to retrieve.
    What I did was create a thread safe array of booleans, and store whether or not a particular thread has finished.
    Then, using multiple threads, I launched a bunch of HTTP requests, and how fast the information comes depends on
    how many threads your phone can simultaneously launch (along with your internet speed). Each thread retrieves the information, and stores it in a database
    on your phone. So at this point, if its slow, just blame your phone. As for how you know how far along the data retrieval is coming,
    well I have another thread monitoring how many of the times have been filled in the array I mentioned earlier. That is what\'s
    causing the updates in the text you see above. Also, because it runs in parallel, you'll see the number suddenly jump up.</string>
</resources>